

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Tehran, Iran

□ (+98) 937-252-4321 | 🗷 danialkhakbaz.dk@gmail.com | 💣 danielkhakbaz.github.io/links/

Summary

23-years-old passionate Front-end Developer with +3 years of experience in the field. Young and Motivated person with a good understanding of Data Structure and Algorithms who loves to learn new technologies and ready to take big challenges. Also, I can code clean and reliable.

Work Experience _____

Front-end Developer | React Developer

Tehran, Iran

BANKID

Aug. 2022 - Present

- BankID is the first e-KYC service provider in Iran which uses powerful AI algorithms including live face detection and verification to authenticate the users' ID, with more than 50,000 daily users and 6,000,000 successful authentications.
- Work on some really challenging concepts and projects including developing re-usable components for our customers to implement them in their code.
- Designed and Developed and also maintained 3 admin-panels with different roles.
- Worked in a fast-paced and demanding environment, tackling complex concepts and projects that required a high degree of precision and attention to detail. Successfully navigated tight deadlines and high-pressure situations, demonstrating strong problem-solving skills and the ability to adapt to changing circumstances.
- Used React.js as the main library for developing UI-interfaces with using ChakraUI and tailwindCSS.
- · Worked both on-site and remotely with the team.

Front-end Developer | React Developer

Tehran, Iran

HADISH SABZ PARSEH

Jul. 2020 - Aug. 2021

- Hadish Sabz Parseh is one of the largest Smart-TV manufacturers in Iran and I was working in the Front-end development department using React. is as the main library for developing UI-interfaces.
- Designed and developed a 2-language shopping website with a focus on improving client experience.
- Build a vertical business-to-business website including 3 admin-panels based on the roles in the company with a certain accessibilities.
- Worked in a Agile-driven environment to effectively maintain project timelines and attending in daily-standup meetings which was a great opportunity to discuss the project with the team.

Front-end Developer | Javascript Developer

Tehran, Iran

CROSS SPORT

Jun. 2019 - Mar. 2020

- CrossSport is one of the largest online store and manufacturer of sports equipment in the country.
- Started off my professional career in a pretty solid team as a Front-end Developer as my first real work-experience.
- Designed and developed websites using Vanilla JS, jQuery with using many UI-Kits.

Skills

- **React.js**, Next.js, Redux
- **Javascript**, Typescript
- **HTML**, CSS, Material-UI, Styled-Components, TailwindCSS, ChakraUI
- **Communication**, Team-work, Problem-solving, Time-management

Projects

Notes App

NEXT.JS, TAILWINDCSS, DAISYUI

• a website for writing and keeping your notes. Developed it using Next.js as the main framework and also used localStorage API as the main storage for keeping the data. You can access to the code from here. And also you can see the demo from here.

Education _____

B.S. in Computer Engineering

Tehran, Iran

ISLAMIC AZAD UNIVERSITY(WEST TEHRAN BRANCH)

2018 - 2023

 Selected courses: Fundamentals of Programming(19/20), Advanced Programming(16/20), Engineering Statistics and Possibilities(20/20), Logic Circuits(19/20), Database(17.5/20), Computer Architecture(19/20), Specialized Language(20/20), Human-Computer interaction(20/20)